http://www.ciu.edu/privacy

Jump to navigation
You are here > Privacy & Policies
Additional Navigation
PoliciesTitle IXStudent DisabilityStudent Rights and ResponsibilitiesStudent Non-Academic GrievanceWithdrawalTuition & Fees RefundFinancial Aid RefundOther Institutional Policies
Privacy & Policies
Privacy & PoliciesColumbia International University (CIU) is required by the U.S. Department of Education to compile and publicize certain consumer information. Additional information may be found in the Academic Catalog and Student Handbook.Privacy PolicyCIU takes seriously the issue of safeguarding your privacy online. The following privacy statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices.What Info CIU CollectsWe collect aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit, as well as information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information and/or site registrations.The information we collect is not shared with any other organization.How CIU Uses CookiesWe use cookies to record session information, such as items that visitors add to their shopping cart. We do not store personal information or credit card numbers in cookies.If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please contact us at webmaster@ciu.edu.How CIU Uses Postal AddressesIf you supply us with your postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please contact us at webmaster@ciu.edu.How CIU Uses Telephone NumbersPersons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding information submitted online.Ad Server PartnershipsWe do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.Information Available to Site VisitorsUpon request we provide site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them. Visitors can access this information by contacting us at webmaster@ciu.edu.If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the addresses or phone number below.We have appropriate security measures in place on our web site to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we may collect from you.How CIU Secures Credit Card NumbersWe have also taken measures to ensure the safety of your credit card use on our site. Orders placed at our online stores are in a secured area. We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all our online stores. SSL is the industry standard and best available secure transaction technology. If you are still uncomfortable transmitting your credit card information over the Internet, you may contact us directly by phone at 1-800-777-2227, and we will assist you in completing your order.Privacy Policy AgreementBy using any of the CIU websites, you signify your assent to the CIU Online Privacy Policy. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes.If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or any other CIU officially related websites, please contact us. Contact CIU7435 Monticello RoadColumbia, SC 292031-800-777-2227webmaster@ciu.edu
